here's a couple lemon slices rainbow
dash put them in that ziplo bag and put
a 99 cent price tag on it damn Applejack
99 cents for two slices of lemons now
that I found out you were this much of a
girl boss consider yourself 20% cooler
thank you jesus Christ two lemon slices
for 99 what a ripoff well thanks again
for reminding us why we all hate you
hey Pinkie Pie you know something that
would be really fun going home no if you
took one of them lemons and squirted
some lemon juice right into Applejack's
eyes okay Pinky hurry before she sees
you
why did you tell me to do that how was I
supposed to know you would hold it
backwards what's that now pinkie Pie
tried squirting a lemon in your eye but
she got it in hers by mistake well
sharks i think that serves her right
pinkie I go home i don't want you
cutting my lemons
anymore now she bit me stop it
hey girlies it's almost time for
Twilight's hair dye appointment who
wants the privilege of coming upstairs
into Applejack's dirty ass bathroom and
doing it with
me look there she is at the end of the
hall hey girl hey i was expecting the
orange one but I suppose this one is
fine has she done this before first time
I think i see well let's hope she's a
fast learner i would hate for the next
one I get rid of to be a member of the
main
six pinkie Pie stop fidgeting i want the
pink streak in my hair to be perfectly
symmetrical with the purple one that
Rarity made do you like it darling i
think the purple rectangle in my hair is
lovely
pinky what did I just tell you i'm
trying this is the seventh time I had to
tell you get it right or I'm having
Rarity do it you know this is a
privilege but she got to do the purple
one i want to do the pink one well
you're not going to be doing either if
you don't do it right girls do you have
any dreams for the pink streak in my
hair to be done I guess my dream has
always been to open up a lemonade stand
your dream is to sell citric acid in a
cup maybe it is kind of a stupid dream i
mean I am 38
take it from me sassy pants you're never
too old to reach for the stars we're not
talking about stars Rarity we're talking
about lemons i was being metaphorical
me and Twilight don't know what that
word means rarity a metaphor is a figure
of speech in which a word or phrase is
applied to an object or action to which
it is not literally applicable yeah it's
a word you can't apply to stuff
well tighten my boots and call me a
flapjack you all done trotted up just in
time for some plank picking this here is
for good stuff i've been stacking and
flipping these timber biscuits and let
me tell you they're tighter than a in a
you all best get to slam jamming these
flatstick flappers into a root and tubed
in lemon box so on it will make a [__]
salivate sideways done you go slouching
none either you got to get your jiggle
jam in gear because I want that box
jumped together tighter than a tub banjo
wedged in a pickle barrel who wore this
wood is ready to be something twilight
darling move 2 in to your left right in
front of the cash box it makes you look
trustworthy perfect now freeze we must
capture the essence of summer sweetness
and subtle economic ambition
you stepped on my hoof [__] now girls
let us not converge upon each other
inappropriately i don't want to get
banned that's rich coming from the town
bicycle with square wheels what's you
say [__] mighty unicorn powers
go yeah Pinky get her purple
ass omg we have one whole viewer my
dedicated superfan that comes to all my
streams golly me Rare Alert is back
online she put out a new vlog after she
got a 2-day suspension for crapping
herself then accidentally flashing her
tits when she bent down to clean it up
her eyeliner is so crisp today i hope
we're doing makeup tutorials wait is
that a lemonade stand does that mean she
is in Ponyville right now
okay we've only been out here for an
hour 34 minutes with zero customers but
I feel like the next pony who walks by
is going to be the one that breaks the
street perhaps we should have offered
more options like letting customers take
a dump on me charlie I'm going to cry
why won't horses financially support me
go for it girl emotional manipulation is
the strongest currency in business next
to a pony in a bikini you know what this
stand needs less lemonade so we can go
home i'm starting to think you don't
even want to be here no this is fun i
love standing under a wobbling sign we
cobbled together with silly string
plucked from Pinky's ass and day old
taco
meat i didn't say anything at the start
because I was emotionally tired but I'll
stay because you're my friends and I
know how much you all love hanging out
with me specifically
thank you so much for not leaving me
alone with her they're there it's okay
i'm here you're safe hey Twilight is it
true that all lemons are sour yes
they're all sour Pinky just like life oh
hi Princess Celestia are you here to buy
some lemonade oh uh actually I'm just uh
here to see Rarity i I noticed you've
been doing a lot of vlogs recently i
think they're really good you know I've
always wanted to try and do some myself
but I don't have a clue where to start
so I've been watching yours as
inspiration oh well thanks I guess
you're welcome hey do you want to
collaborate with me we could make one
together wouldn't that be fun not really
oh yeah um okay are you okay princess
why did you take off your hood no
particular reason while I'm going home
it was really great talking to you
Rarity i guess I can't wait to see what
you come up with for your next video if
you ever do want to collab thanks
princess but I already have the next few
planned out oh okay but if you change
your mind no really I'm good
okay for the record just because I'm old
it doesn't mean I can't be fun
too i'm going to unfollow you on your
blog because it's obvious you don't
respect your one follower
oh boy sour beverages to quench my
thirst
twilight that pony is a part of
Ponyville's assisted living program i
know don't laugh this is my best friend
Jinx i met her 14 minutes ago at the
residential care facility that I go to
weekly to have my mental disabilities
tested to see if they are improving they
never do but I made a good friend out of
those visits she's quadripollegic which
means she can't move from the neck down
so she has no choice to be my friend
whether she likes it or not because I
can take her with me wherever I go with
her wheelchair also she is mute so she
is not very opinionated it's her
birthday and she is finally leaving the
foster care system yay oh that's great
she was adopted no she just turned 18 so
she's getting kicked out well let's make
her day even better with this nice warm
picture of Lemonade tell the customer
what I told you Pinkie Pie would you
like a glass of my piss what i mean
lemonade haha you're such a silly little
pony hm i don't know $7 for some sour
sugar water is quite a lot for something
I can make myself yeah but would you ha
you got us there she said $7 jinx pull
out your wallet i said
$7 hey you get back
here sorry about that i'm sure now you
can see why she was never adopted jinx
can be a handful but that's why we love
her and by we I mean just me because I'm
the only one who likes her it's okay
Jinx i'll treat you this time but you'll
have to pay me back later wow this is
really good it's so salty and nice salty
the best lemonade I've ever had salty
doesn't sound like citric acid i'm doing
it girls my dream is coming true
twilight Derpy gave us Monopoly money
i'm more worried about Derpy liking
something that is not a good sign
why does it taste like goddamn piss i
got to be honest with you girlfriend i
forgot to bring any lemons so I just
peed in a bunch of jars
then what are all these they're cake
balls I painted to look like lemons wow
they look so realistic you forgot the
lemons but you had enough time to paint
like 15 cake balls i have a lot of free
time but not enough time in the world it
seems to do anything right where are you
going i'm going home to eat my cake
balls
is that Rainbow Dash oh my god she's
setting up her own stall
i'll go talk to her pinky piss
what is up Sparkle [__]
i know you're not about to start a turf
war with another lemonade stand i'm
built different from that cotton candy
[__] i've got homemade cookies out the
ass over here these aren't homemade you
bought them from Pinkie Pie's bakery no
I stole them you know how she upcharges
i would never pay her prices you want a
free sample
i will not fall for your friendship ploy
twilight this will be your one and only
chance to try a cookie from Sugar Cube
Corner for under $115
she's not going anywhere but she did
give us some free samples i'm the baker
here i will be the judge
damn this tastes like
[__] looks like we've got nothing to
worry about
girls oh no Rainbow Dash is using
Fluttershy's sex appeal to her advantage
all of Ponyville is lining up to see her
bounce her tits like water balloons
quick Twilight you can think of
something you've saved Equestria nine
times before yeah but I've never been up
against Fluttershy in a bikini what if I
go home and put on a bikini too or
here's a crazy idea you go home and grab
some lemons and bring them back here and
start selling some gosh darn lemonade
like we planned
l O L What the [__] now why in the name
of Celestia are you crying because you
yelled at me while I was trying to
achieve my dreams your dream was to sell
lemonade you spent 7 hours this morning
painting cake balls and pissing in jars
and selling them for $7 that's it i
don't need to hear this from you i'm
packing up my kickballs and going home
that's fine i don't want to be out here
anyway it's like 90° i can already feel
the sweat pooling up in my butt crack
and mixing with my [__] to form some
sort of pungent marinade you're with me
too right rarity rarity
rarity where are you i went home to
watch My Little Pony when like 10
minutes ago after I saw Fluttershy in
the bikini i knew we weren't getting any
more business after that you left me
alone with Pinkie Pie who has the
mentality of a 2-year-old
twilight look there's chocolate in my
diaper where did it come from pinkie Pie
no don't eat that
yo Pinks where the [__] you going i'm
going home oh what's the matter have a
bad day you want to talk about a bad day
try standing in the sun for seven hours
with lemon cake pops just to get your
ass handed to you by a bunch of traders
selling cookies on the other side of the
road with Fluttershy whipping out her
huge lemony yellow bunka
dock you know what I realized ponies
don't want effort i put in so much
effort today but they just want lots and
lots of fat ass cheeks they can slap
around well not all of us can be born a
bad ass with a fat ass like our main
girl Flutter Butter pinkie Pie you put
more effort spending hours making cake
pops to trick people when you could have
just went to the store and bought lemons
to make lemonade why would I do that
when I'm a baker the same reason you're
a racist [__] despite being part of the
inferior race dear you know a pony can
do multiple things multiple things like
how a toilet can be used to both pee in
and drink free water from you drink
toilet water only when it's backed up
and full to the top with piss and [__]
so no pony notices pinky you need to
stop talking we are learning so many
things about you today pinkie Pie have
you ever thought that maybe you're not
as special as you think you are
you want to say that to my face
what's the matter sis you look like
you've hit rock bottom
yeah you seem like you're stuck between
a rock and a hard place lately I've been
wondering why I'm not gray like rocks
like the rest of you girls
she's right technically pink is not a
naturally occurring pigment in most
rocks if it is there it's being caused
by other elements like
titanium the pony equivalent of that is
likely to be a form of mental
retardation well not every pony can be
born a badass with a fat ass pinkie Pie
it doesn't matter that you're pink like
Below Knee do you know what it means
that mommy is a cheating [__] yeah but
it also means you're unique not every
family has a bastard child that looks
like cotton candy i don't want to be
unique i want to be normal
sweet baby horse Jesus is that what I
think it is it's pink just like me but I
don't understand i thought all rocks
were gray and boring as [__] just like
you mod high quality quartz probably
volcanic could be worth a lot of money
maybe we can split it and escape the
rock farm together see Pinky you are a
rock just a different kind you do belong
here no it means I'm better than you
[__] if what Ma said is true this
[__] could finally be my ticket out of
this dump i'll buy a cake shop in some
far off town and make little cakes for
little ponies like [__] hell you are
you dumb [__] nut bimbo [__] you can't
just [__] leave you're the fourth
[__] member of our [__] group
we're like the [__] Teletubbies or
the Fantastic [__] Four if they
didn't [__] suck don't pay her any
mind Limestone she'll come back she
always does once in a while we all dream
of leaving this farm but the rocks
always call us back these rocks are our
home and we have no choice but to obey
their call yeah right and by the way I
would say who I hate the most but I hate
you all equally you know what i changed
my mind ma you are the [__] worst me
and the other girls trash talk you
behind your back every day that really
sucks to hear because I seriously love
you guys marble you are the only one I
don't want to strangle to death but
that's only because you don't talk to me
hell you don't talk to anybody you're
like a rock you're bland and boring this
whole family is boring we're not boring
now let's go inside and watch Avatar the
Last Airbender by Might Shyamalan or
Dragon Ball Evolution which are the
better versions of the cartoon limestone
I take back everything I said about Ma
you are the [__] worst do you want to
elaborate on that before I [__] you in
the butthole sideways and make you call
me mommy you know what you [__] did
but I won't bring it up because if our
sisters ever found about your sinister
deeds you would be kicked out of this
godforsaken family you [__]
piece of [__] you think I give a damn i
[__] own you this is a house of Jesus
Christ but you act like the [__]
devil we all live in fear of you as you
should girls the normal school bus is
here for marble pie pie and limestone
pie and the short one is here for Pinkie
Pie pinky the day is not over yet let's
go to your house i got a game we can all
play that should cheer you right up what
are we going to do we're going to take
turns having a whole lot of fun with
those pink plump butt cheeks
thanks for dropping by Pinkie Pie's
lemonade stand
twilight why does this taste like Pinkie
Pie's piss just deal with it we're doing
this for our friend wait is this
actually piss hey where's my money this
is just a roleplay Pinkie Pie no you're
roleplaying i'm running a business okay
girl damn I hear you this is Derpy's
Monopoly money mama wants real
currency this is only $7 that's what the
sign says but there's an upcharge of $9
because you're in my house you're paying
for the nice scenery pinkie Pie there is
a fresh turd that you recently produced
in the corner of the hallway that half
of us stepped on coming in here uh-oh
we're out of lemonade i'd better go in
the bathroom and make some more
cheese and crackers have we all been
drinking this let's make off like this
ourselves then and piss off you can't go
we promised Pinkie Pie that we would
stay in
i'm back with more Golden Delicious
where is every pony twilight where did
every pony go tell me the truth i swear
I can take it they went home oh oh my
god don't be sad it's okay i'm used to
this kind of treatment being poor old
Pinkie Pie i know you don't want to
drink my piss either you can go home
pinkie Pie can I ask you a question no
why are you still pissing in the picture
to make lemonade when we're back at your
house with your fridge full of lemons
well it's sort of an embarrassing story
with all due respect I'd like to know
why I'm drinking your piss like some
sort of piss baby
you know when we were cutting up lemon
slices to sell on the side of the road
while you were upstairs in Apple Jack's
dirty bathroom yeah that place was
really gross well while you were up
there the girls they bullied me the girl
tried to shoot lemon juice in my eye
string her up girls she is getting 50
lashes applejack stop you're taking this
way too far so you're with her girls
string Rarity up too oh
I have to be honest about something i
saw the whole thing too from the
upstairs bathroom window i could have
intervened but I was prepping to have my
hair dyed and the back of the bottle
said I had to leave the conditioner in
for at least 15 minutes so I chose to
not go out there to help you but I see
now that maybe I should have especially
since the moment seemed to have awoken a
nightmarish fear of lemons within you
well now that we can both admit this is
your fault I think you owe me like a
bonding moment where we make some actual
lemonade i was thinking more like money
how much do you want how much do you
have on you
what are you doing here Jinx where's
Derpy how did you even get here look
Twilight there's a letter in the
cripple's lap dear Pinkie Pie I hear
that lately you've been feeling a bit
sour dear Pinkie Pie oh she's going to
read it i hear that lately you've been
feeling a bit sour you believe you are
too [__] to chase your dreams but
let me tell you girl nobody is too
[__] to reach their dreams ponies
like you and me just have to reach for
dreams that are much easier to get my
own parents used to tell me I would get
nowhere in life well look at me now i
wash dishes at the local Applebees on
weekdays and I'm also an overnight
stalker at Walmart on the weekends
that's two whole jobs you remind me a
whole lot of Derpy Pinky derpy is a
loser she's ugly as [__] and thought no
pony would ever love her but I took that
shot and tried being her friend even
though she's ugly as [__] and it is the
best damn thing this [__] has ever
done if I can become friends with that
crosseyed [__] [__] then I believe
you can become friends with lemons again
someday
what's she doing i think she wants you
to turn it over
oh Jinx baby girl we're we're kind of
busy at the moment why don't you roll
along down the hill and come back later
what no I don't want her coming back to
my house roll along down the hill but
don't come back
okay heat heat
heat heat heat